Guide to the National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (NABET-CWA) Records WAG.197
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Bargaining Files, 1959-1995
  - Subseries II:A: National Networks, 1959-1988
    - NBC: Strike-Law Suit, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - NBC: Strike-Law Suit, Strike Benefits, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - NBC: Strike-Legal Correspondence, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - NBC: Strike-Letters of Agreement, Misconduct, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - NBC: Strike-NBC Radio Networks Sale, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - NBC: Strike-National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Case, Atlantic City Convention Center, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - NBC: Strike-NLRB Case, Employee Benefits, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - NBC: Strike-NLRB Case, Implementation of Contract, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - NBC: Strike-NLRB Case, KPNX-Phoenix, AZ, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - NBC: Strike-NLRB Case, Local 53, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - NBC: Strike-NLRB Case, Mile High Stadium-Denver, CO, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - NBC: Strike-NLRB Case, Negotiations, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - NBC: Strike-NLRB Case, News-writer Decertification, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - NBC: Strike-NLRB Case, New York Yankees Corporation, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - NBC: Strike-NLRB Case, Papal Visit-Los Angeles, CA, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - NBC: Strike-NLRB Case, Tiger Stadium-Detroit, MI, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - NBC: Strike-Negotiations, Status Reports, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - NBC: Strike-News Articles, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - NBC: Strike-Other Union Contracts with NBC, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - NBC: Strike-Picketing, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - NBC: Strike-Picketing, Reserved Gates, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - NBC: Strike-Placards (I), 1987 (Flat-file-folder 1)
    - NBC: Strike-Placards (II), 1987 (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - NBC: Strike-Preliminary Injunctions, Local 53, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - NBC: Strike-Re-employment Waiver and General Release Agreement, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - NBC: Strike-Sponsor Contact, Local 53, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - NBC: Strike-WMAQ, Temporary Restraining Order, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - NBC: Strike-Mailings, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - NBC: Strike-Material Sent to Donahue Show, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - NBC: Strike-Medical Benefits Paid During Strike, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Subseries II:B: Local Affiliates, 1974-1995
    - CA: KCOY, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - CA: KCOY, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - CA: KERO, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - CA: KFI, 1979-1989 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - CA: KMEX, 1982-1989 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - CA: KPIX, 1983-1986 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - CA: KQED (I), 1975-1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - CA: KQED (II), 1975-1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - CA: KSFO, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - CA: KTTV, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - CO: KCNC, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - CO: KOA/KOAQ, 1980-1987 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - CT: WFSB (I), 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - CT: WFSB (II), 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - CT: WFSB (III), 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - CT: WFSB (IV), 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - CT: WFSB (V), 1986-1990 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - DC: PBS, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - DC: WHMM (I), 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - DC: WHMM (II), 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - DC: WJLA, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - FL: WIOD, 1979-1988 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - FL: WSVN (I), 1985-1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - FL: WSVN (II), 1985-1992 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - FL: WSVN (III), 1985-1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - FL: WSVN (IV), 1985-1992 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - FL: WSVN (V), 1985-1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - FL: WTVJ, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - IL: WCIU, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - IL: WLS, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - MA: WGGB, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - MI: WCMU/WCML, 1980-1990 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - MI: WEYI, 1978-1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - MI: WFDF (I), 1981-1988 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - MI: WFDF (II), 1981-1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - MI: WFLT/WAAM, 1980-1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - MI: WJBK, 1980-1989 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - MI: WJIM, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - MI: WJIM (includes ACLU brief) (I), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - MI: WJIM (includes ACLU brief) (II), 1977 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - MI: WJIM, 1978-1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - MI: WJRT, 1980-1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - MI: WTAC (I), 1978-1986 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - MI: WTAC (II), 1978-1986 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - MI: WTRX (I), 1978-1989 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - MI: WTRX (II), 1978-1989 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - MI: WNEM, 1981-1989 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - MI: WWCK (I), 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - MI: WWCK (II), 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - MI: WWTV, 1982-1990 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - MI: WXON (I), 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - MI: WXON (II), 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - MN: KTCA/KTCI, 1981-1995 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - MN: WCCO, 1979-1990 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - NE: KETV, 1983-1990 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - NE: KMTV, 1973-1983 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - NE: KMTV, 1984-1989 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - NE: KMTV, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - NE: KMTV (I), 1993 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - NE: KMTV (II), 1993 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - NE: KMTV, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - NE: KMTV (I), 1995 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - NE: KMTV (II), 1995 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - NE: KMTV (III), 1995 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - NE: KMTV (IV), 1995 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - NY: WFAS, 1988-1992 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - NY: WGRZ (I), 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - NY: WGRZ (II), 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - NY: WIBV, 1986-1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - NY: WICZ, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - NY: WIXT, 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - NY: WKBW, 1985-1992 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - NY: WOR, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - NY: WRGB, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - NY: WRKL, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - NY: WRKS, 1989-1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - NY: WSKG, 1984-1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - NY: WSTM, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - NY: WTVH, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - NY: WTVH, 1990-1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - NY: WUTV, 1977-1985 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - OH: WCPO, 1979-1992 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - OH: WFMJ, 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - OH: WFMJ, 1985-1990 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - OH: WJKW (Storer Broadcasting Company), 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - OH: WJKW (Storer Broadcasting Company), 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - OH: WJKW (Storer Broadcasting Company) (I), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - OH: WJKW (Storer Broadcasting Company) (II), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - OH: WJKW (Storer Broadcasting Company) (III), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - OH: WJKW (Storer Broadcasting Company) (IV), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - OH: WJKW (Storer Broadcasting Company) (V), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - OH: WJKW (Storer Broadcasting Company) (I), 1984 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - OH: WJKW (Storer Broadcasting Company) (II), 1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - OH: WJKW (Storer Broadcasting Company), 1985 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - OH: WKBN, 1980-1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - OH: WVIZ, 1978-1987 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - OH: WWWE/WDOK, 1984-1987 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - OH: WYTV, 1980-1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - PA: WICU, 1988-1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - PA: WITF (I), 1987-1992 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - PA: WITF (II), 1987-1992 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - PA: WITF (III), 1987-1992 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - PA: WITF (IV), 1987-1992 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - PA: WSEE, 1986-1992 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - TN: WPTY, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - WV: WTRF, 1989-1992 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - WV: WWOK (I), 1989-1993 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - WV: WWOK (II), 1989-1993 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Series III: Archived Websites, March 2009-ongoing; 2 websites in two archived websites.
  Scope and Content Note
  National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians-Communications Workers of America (NABET-CWA), founded in 1934, is a Union of workers who are employed in the broadcasting, distributing, telecasting, recording, cable, video, sound recording and related industries in North America. NABET-CWA has contracts with ABC, NBC, FOX and other networks, as well as local TV stations across the country and members include engineers, photographers, editors, directors, technicians, graphic artists, traffic coordinators, clerical workers, truck operators, writers, reporters, anchors, producers and others in the television and cable industry. The website includes news and event listings, their newsletters, training materials, and audiovisual materials.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued semiannually.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of http://www.nabetcwa.org/ and https://www.nabetcwasports.org/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints. Scope was expanded to include Wix elements in the website.